{
    "questions": [{
        "question": "What year was Trinity founded?",
            "1": "1910",
            "2": "1709",
            "3": "1802",
            "4": "1950",
            "5": "1800",
            "correct": "1709"
    }, {
        "question": "What is Trinity's student:teacher ratio?",
            "1": "6:1",
            "2": "5:1",
            "3": "10:1",
            "correct": "6:1"
    }, {
        "question": "What are Trinity's school colors?",
            "1": "Blue and Gold",
            "2": "White and Blue",
            "3": "Green and Gold",
            "4": "Purple and White",
            "correct": "Blue and Gold"
    }, {
        "question": "How big is the Trinity senate?",
            "1": "8 students",
            "2": "4 students",
            "3": "16 students",
            "correct": "16 students"
    }, {
        "question": "How many varsity teams does the upper school have in the winter season?",
            "1": "8 teams",
            "2": "6 teams",
            "3": "4 teams",
            "4": "5 teams",
            "5": "7 teams",
            "correct": "6 teams"
    }, {
        "question": "On what street is Trinity located?",
            "1": "91st st",
            "2": "100th",
            "3": "84th",
            "correct": "91st"
    }, {
        "question": "On what floor is Trinity's math lab",
            "1": "The first floor",
            "2": "The third floor",
            "3": "The second floor",
            "4": "The basement",
            "correct": "The second floor"
    }, {
        "question": "How many semester(s) of art does the Upper School require?",
            "1": "Three semesters",
            "2": "One semester",
            "3": "Two semesters",
            "4": "No semesters of art are required",
            "correct": "Three semesters"
    }, {
        "question": "How many pool(s) does Trinity have?",
            "1": "One pool",
            "2": "Two pools",
            "3": "No pools",
            "correct": "Two pools"
    }, {
        "question": "Which Canadian province is part of Trinity's global travel program?",
            "1": "British Columbia",
            "2": "Ontario",
            "3": "Quebec",
            "correct": "Quebec"
    }] // End array.                                  

} // End quiz